<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LTE Coverage Tool</string>

    <!-- Disclaimer Screen. -->
    <string name="activity_disclaimer_liability_notice_link_text">Disclaimer of Liability Notice</string>
    <string name="activity_disclaimer_prohibition_notice_link_text">Prohibition on Use Notice</string>
    <string name="activity_disclaimer_acknowledgement_notice_link_text">Acknowledgement Notice</string>
    <string name="activity_disclaimer_nist_licensing_statement_link_text">NIST Licensing Statement</string>
    <string name="activity_disclaimer_uncertainty_statement_link_text">Uncertainty Statement</string>
    <string name="activity_disclaimer_exit_button_text">Exit</string>
    <string name="activity_disclaimer_accept_button_text">Accept</string>

    <!-- Liability Notice Screen. -->
    <string name="activity_liability_notice_title_text"><u>DISCLAIMER OF LIABILITY NOTICE</u></string>
    <string name="activity_liability_notice_body_text">
        The United States Government shall not be liable or responsible for any maintenance, updating or for correction of any errors in the software.\n\n

        THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED “AS IS” WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESSED, IMPLIED, OR STATUTORY,
        INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, ANY WARRANTY THAT THE SOFTWARE WILL CONFORM TO SPECIFICATIONS, ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A
        PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR FREEDOM FROM INFRINGEMENT, ANY WARRANTY THAT THE SOFTWARE WILL BE ERROR FREE, OR ANY WARRANTY THAT THE DOCUMENTATION, IF PROVIDED,
        WILL CONFORM TO THE SOFTWARE.  IN NO EVENT SHALL THE UNITED STATES GOVERNMENT OR ITS CONTRACTORS OR SUBCONTRACTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES, INCLUDING,
        BUT NOT LIMITED TO, DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, ARISING OUT OF, RESULTING FROM, OR IN ANY WAY CONNECTED WITH THE SOFTWARE OR ANY
        OTHER PROVIDED DOCUMENTATION, WHETHER OR NOT BASED UPON WARRANTY, CONTRACT, TORT, OR OTHERWISE, WHETHER OR NOT INJURY WAS SUSTAINED BY PERSONS OR PROPERTY
        OR OTHERWISE, AND WHETHER OR NOT LOSS WAS SUSTAINED FROM, OR AROSE OUT OF THE RESULTS OF, OR USE OF, THE SOFTWARE OR ANY PROVIDED DOCUMENTATION. THE
        UNITED STATES GOVERNMENT DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES AND LIABILITIES REGARDING THIRD PARTY SOFTWARE, IF PRESENT IN THE SOFTWARE, AND DISTRIBUTES IT “AS IS.”\n\n

        LICENSEE AGREES TO WAIVE ANY AND ALL CLAIMS AGAINST THE U.S. GOVERNMENT AND THE UNITED STATES GOVERNMENT’S CONTRACTORS AND SUBCONTRACTORS, AND SHALL
        INDEMNIFY AND HOLD HARMLESS THE U.S. GOVERNMENT AND THE UNITED STATES GOVERNMENT’S CONTRACTORS AND SUBCONTRACTORS FOR ANY LIABILITIES, DEMANDS, DAMAGES,
        EXPENSES, OR LOSSES THAT MAY ARISE FROM RECIPIENT’S USE OF THE SOFTWARE OR PROVIDED DOCUMENTATION, INCLUDING ANY LIABILITIES OR DAMAGES FROM PRODUCTS BASED
        ON, OR RESULTING FROM, THE USE THEREOF.
    </string>


    <!-- Prohibition Notice Screen. -->
    <string name="activity_prohibition_notice_title_text"><u>PROHIBITION ON USE OF DHS IDENTITIES NOTICE</u></string>
    <string name="activity_prohibition_notice_body_text">
        A.  No user shall use the DHS or its component name, seal or other identity, or any variation or adaptation thereof, for an enhancement, improvement,
        modification or derivative work utilizing the software.\n\n

        B.  No user shall use the DHS or its component name, seal or other identity, or any variation or adaptation thereof for advertising its products or
        services, with the exception of using a factual statement such as included in the ACKNOWLEDGEMENT NOTICE indicating DHS funding of development of the software.\n\n

        C.  No user shall make any trademark claim to the DHS or its component name, seal or other identity, or any other confusing similar identity, and no
        user shall seek registration of these identities at the U.S. Patent and Trademark Office.
    </string>

    <!-- Acknowledgement Notice Screen. -->
    <string name="activity_acknowledgement_notice_title_text"><u>ACKNOWLEDGEMENT NOTICE</u></string>
    <string name="activity_acknowledgement_notice_body_text">
        This software was developed with funds from the Department of Homeland Security’s Science and Technology Directorate.
    </string>

    <!-- NIST Software Screen. -->
    <string name="activity_nist_software_title_text"><u>NIST Software</u></string>
    <string name="activity_nist_software_body_text">
        This software was developed by employees of the National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST), an agency of the Federal Government
        and is being made available as a public service. Pursuant to title 17 United States Code Section 105, works of NIST employees are not
        subject to copyright protection in the United States.  This software may be subject to foreign copyright.  Permission in the United States
        and in foreign countries, to the extent that NIST may hold copyright, to use, copy, modify, create derivative works, and distribute
        this software and its documentation without fee is hereby granted on a non-exclusive basis, provided that this notice and disclaimer of
        warranty appears in all copies.\n\n

        THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED \'AS IS\' WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESSED, IMPLIED, OR STATUTORY, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO,
        ANY WARRANTY THAT THE SOFTWARE WILL CONFORM TO SPECIFICATIONS, ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE,
        AND FREEDOM FROM INFRINGEMENT, AND ANY WARRANTY THAT THE DOCUMENTATION WILL CONFORM TO THE SOFTWARE, OR ANY WARRANTY THAT THE SOFTWARE WILL
        BE ERROR FREE.  IN NO EVENT SHALL NIST BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL
        DAMAGES, ARISING OUT OF, RESULTING FROM, OR IN ANY WAY CONNECTED WITH THIS SOFTWARE, WHETHER OR NOT BASED UPON WARRANTY, CONTRACT, TORT, OR OTHERWISE,
        WHETHER OR NOT INJURY WAS SUSTAINED BY PERSONS OR PROPERTY OR OTHERWISE, AND WHETHER OR NOT LOSS WAS SUSTAINED FROM, OR AROSE OUT OF THE RESULTS OF,
        OR USE OF, THE SOFTWARE OR SERVICES PROVIDED HEREUNDER.
    </string>

    <!-- Uncertainty Notice Screen. -->
    <string name="activity_uncertainty_notice_title_text"><u>Uncertainty Statement</u></string>
    <string name="activity_uncertainty_notice_body_text">
        Values are assumed to be accurate within ±8 dB for RSRP or ±3.5 dB for RSRQ, for a UE complying with 3GPP standard TR36.133 sections 9.1.2, 9.1.3,
        9.1.5 and 9.1.6, operating under the following conditions:\n\n

        1. Cell specific reference signals are transmitted either from one, two or four antenna ports.\n\n
        2. Conditions defined in 36.101 Clause 7.3 for reference sensitivity are fulfilled.\n\n
        3. RSRP|dBm according to Annex B.3.1 or B.3.3, as appropriate, for a corresponding Band.\n\n
        4. Normal condition, as defined by 3GPP.
    </string>

    <!-- New Recording Screen. -->
    <string name="activity_new_recording_offset_label_text">Offset (dB)</string>
    <string name="activity_new_recording_new_recording_button_text">New Recording</string>

    <!-- Record Screen. -->
    <string name="activity_record_signal_strength_label_text">Signal Strength</string>
    <string name="activity_record_pause_button_text">Pause</string>
    <string name="activity_record_resume_button_text">Resume</string>
    <string name="activity_record_stop_button_text">Stop</string>
    <string name="activity_record_record_image_label_text">RECORDING...</string>
    <string name="activity_record_recording_paused_image_label_text">PAUSE</string>
    <string name="activity_record_lte_rsrp_label_text">LTE RSRP (dBm)*</string>
    <string name="activity_record_lte_rsrq_label_text">LTE RSRQ (dBm)*</string>
    <string name="activity_record_lte_pci_label_text">LTE PCI</string>
    <string name="activity_record_data_points_label_text">Data points</string>
    <string name="activity_record_offset_label_text">Offset (dB)</string>
    <string name="activity_record_uncertainty_statement_text"><u>*Uncertainty Statement</u></string>
    <string name="activity_record_signal_strength_excellent">Excellent</string>
    <string name="activity_record_signal_strength_good">Good</string>
    <string name="activity_record_signal_strength_poor">Poor</string>
    <string name="activity_record_signal_strength_no_signal">No Signal</string>

    <!-- Display Results Activity. -->
    <string name="title_activity_display_results">DisplayResults</string>
    <string name="activity_display_results_grade_tab_text">Grade</string>
    <string name="activity_display_results_line_chart_tab_text">Line Chart</string>
    <string name="activity_display_results_filename_label_text">Filename</string>

    <!-- Grade Fragment. -->
    <string name="fragment_grade_grade_label_text">GRADE</string>
    <string name="fragment_grade_pie_chart_label_top">Excellent</string>
    <string name="fragment_grade_pie_chart_label_mid">Good</string>
    <string name="fragment_grade_pie_chart_label_low">Poor</string>


</resources>
